[{"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UNIWA"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.0", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}, "price": "\u20ab1,592,214"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Snapdragon 860"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "24MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4700", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ax,802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "Rotatable,BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "K30 pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab5,469,436"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SERVO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.0", "Display Resolution": "960x400", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"OTG": "yes", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab3,889,134"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.47", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP,108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224832MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "30w"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Version": "Globan ROM", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "cc9 pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab4,618,635"}, {"price": "\u20ab3,965,463"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.15", "Display Resolution": "1170 x 2532", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2815", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card+1 eSIM"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"battery health": "> 90%", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Apple Model": "iPhone 12 Pro", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab18,857,157"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.79\"", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "50MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "Other", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge,USB-PD", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"ROM": "512GB", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ax,802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 240 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS,pse", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab24,308,119"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.26", "Display Resolution": "1080x2280", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "24MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2900", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/Blue/Gold", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Mi 8 Lite", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 660", "Built in radiator": "no"}, "price": "\u20ab3,249,088"}, {"price": "\u20ab8,264,683"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "3.0inch", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "Watch", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "unihertz Model": "Jelly 2e", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}, "price": "\u20ab4,557,620"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Sony"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "2520x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3140", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "JP(Origin)", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab5,321,640"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OPPO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.3", "Display Resolution": "1080x2340", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP,16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "Helio P60", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "OPPO Model": "A7x", "Built in radiator": "no"}, "price": "\u20ab2,254,137"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.5", "Display Resolution": "1170x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Doogee Model": "S mini"}, "price": "\u20ab6,215,953"}, {"price": "\u20ab6,219,357"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "3040x1140", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Super AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "10MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3400", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Camera Type": "3 Back & 1 Front Cameras", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Samsung Model": "S10E", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "Language": "Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab4,621,309"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Flexible Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "MIUI 13"}, "Other": {"Network Access Model": "22101316C", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab10,636,162"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Infinix"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.82 inch", "Display Resolution": "1640x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"google play store": "support", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "6000-7499mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,Arabic,Portuguese,Spanish"}, "price": "\u20ab3,422,652"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "HONOR"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen,Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "40W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"CPU": "Snapdragon 695", "Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}, "price": "\u20ab8,160,642 - \u20ab9,549,635"}, {"price": "\u20ab6,152,022"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1440x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "8000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "GSM,WCDMA,LTE", "NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "OUKITEL Model": "WP5", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Display size range": "Compact (5.5-5.99\")", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "CPU Core Quantity": "Quad Core"}, "price": "\u20ab3,889,134"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SOYES"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "480*854", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1900mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Features 2": "4G LTE Small Smartphone", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Video recording resolution": "HD (720p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6737", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab3,330,036"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "12.4\u201d", "Display Resolution": "1620x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3500", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Blackberry Model": "KEYONE", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab4,456,740"}, {"price": "\u20ab820,270"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Samsung"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "1080x2400", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,5mp,\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224832MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Samsung Model": "A53", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab6,828,773"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1440x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "8000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "GSM,WCDMA,LTE", "NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Display size range": "Compact (5.5-5.99\")", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "CPU Core Quantity": "Octa Core"}, "price": "\u20ab4,861,478"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Hisense"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "1560x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Release date": "2022.5.11", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}, "price": "\u20ab8,969,875"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "FlashCharge", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi K60", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}, "price": "\u20ab9,723,199"}, {"price": "\u20ab820,270"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ax", "Design": "Flip", "": "none", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G25", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab4,861,235"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.81\u201c", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0,USB-PD,Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "xiaomi", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab9,844,985"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "2040x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "5", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "": "295369929", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab6,076,908"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Huawei"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.75", "Display Resolution": "720 x 1600", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "22.5W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "HarmonyOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "6000-7499mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Huawei Model": "Enjoy 60"}, "price": "\u20ab4,173,121"}, {"price": "\u20ab1,327,811"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.35''", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"CPU": "Adreno 512", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "note 7 pro", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab4,980,590"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "AGM"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Can be applied to": "oil and gas exploration, production, transportation, and storage,", "Biometrics Technology": "Rear-mounted", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab7,268,273"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SOYES"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Official Standard": "Yes (Charger Not Included)", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "HD (720p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6750", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab2,835,599"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.45", "Display Resolution": "1440x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4860", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport,Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab3,654,799"}, {"price": "\u20ab820,270"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OPPO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.44", "Display Resolution": "1080x2400", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP,8MP,16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3700", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Blue/Orange/Silver", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian", "OPPO Model": "F17", "Built in radiator": "no"}, "price": "\u20ab2,847,024"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "HONOR"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67\"", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "40W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "honor Model": "x9A", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}, "price": "\u20ab18,103,104"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.2", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2610", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Blackberry Model": "dtek50", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab2,469,997"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.8", "Display Resolution": "2436x1125", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "7MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2716", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Apple Model": "X", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}, "price": "\u20ab6,250,958"}, {"price": "\u20ab2,845,310"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Hotwav"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10800", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Hotwav Model": "Cyber 13 Pro"}, "price": "\u20ab5,945,885"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Spredtrum"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.99", "Display Resolution": "960x480", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5900", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no"}, "price": "\u20ab6,076,908"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52\"", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Memory": "8GB RAM+128GB ROM", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "OUKITEL Model": "WP23 PRO", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab4,514,108"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.45''", "Display Resolution": "720 x 1440 HD+", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4860mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab7,109,052"}, {"price": "\u20ab2,845,310"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.81\u201c", "Display Resolution": "2460x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Display size range": "Large (6.5-7\")", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "LG Model": "stylo 6", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab4,499,037"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.81\u201c", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0,USB-PD,Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "xiaomi 11 pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab9,844,985"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.7", "Display Resolution": "1334x750", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "7MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1821", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card+1 eSIM"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Apple Model": "iPhone SE", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab7,219,170"}, {"price": "\u20ab6,698,868"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "fuffi"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "2.5", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "3MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "30w"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab948,036"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.7", "Display Resolution": "1334x750", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1715", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Front Camera": "5MP", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Apple Model": "iPhone 6S", "Language": "German,Polish,French,Norwegian,Turkish,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese,Russian,English"}, "price": "\u20ab3,058,266"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OPPO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53", "Display Resolution": "1080x2340", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp,2MP,8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3700", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/White", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "Helio P90", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian", "OPPO Model": "Reno2 Z", "Built in radiator": "no"}, "price": "\u20ab4,216,814"}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "2532x1170", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,24MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2815", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Apple Model": "iPhone 12 Pro", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}, "price": "\u20ab16,794,329"}, {"price": "\u20ab1,364,006"}]